warmoth.com 2012-10-04

# Warmoth Custom Guitar Parts - Privacy Notice

**Privacy and Security Policy**

This Privacy Policy discusses what information Warmoth Guitar Products, Inc. collects and how Warmoth Guitar Products, Inc. uses it. By using the Warmoth.com site, you agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

**Information Warmoth collects**  
When you visit the Warmoth.com website, Warmoth receives and collects certain information depending on what you do and how your browser security is set.

*** Information Collected Automatically:** Some information we receive is automatically collected from you when you visit the Warmoth.com site. We receive the name of the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; the browser software you use and your operating system; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. The information we automatically capture provides us the ability to enhance your search and shopping experience and gives us data on overall customer usage patterns.

*** Information Collected by Cookies:** "Cookies" are small text files placed on your computer's hard drive when your browser settings allow them. They collect information about what Warmoth.com webpages you have visited, and in turn, we can provide you customized content. Through the information in cookies we can remember your name and account and keep track of items in your shopping cart so you don’t have to re-enter it everytime you log on. You can disable cookies in your browser settings or you can choose to have your browser warn you every time a cookie is being sent to you. If you refuse all cookies, you will not be able to open a Warmoth.com Shopping Cart and therefore will not be able to complete an order with us online.

*** Information You Actively Submit to Warmoth.com:** For browsing Warmoth.com we neither require nor collect personal information (your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, phone number and credit card information). You can browse the Warmoth.com site and take as much time as you want to review our products without having to submit such personal information. Even when you use our shopping cart as you browse, there is no need to submit personal customer information. However, you do need to submit personal customer information: when you want to   
(1) create an account;   
(2) complete an order;   
(3) subscribe to our newsletter,   
(4) submit customer reviews.

**How Your Information Is Used**

**Proper Order Fulfillment** – correct billing and shipping address, email account, valid credit card number, daytime phone number are all required for fast and accurate fulfillment of your Warmoth order.

**Newsletter** – If you select to receive the newsletter we will send it to your email address on record. 

**Credit card companies** – Our credit card transactions are handled by a third-party financial institution which receives the credit card number and other personal identifying information in order to verify the credit card numbers and process the transactions.

**Law Enforcement Agencies** \- Warmoth Guitar Products, Inc. may release personal customer information when we believe, in our good judgment, that such release is reasonable and necessary to comply with law enforcement and to protect the rights, property, or safety of Warmoth Guitar Products, Inc., our users, or others.

**Other Trustworthy Third Parties** \- From time to time we may share with third parties our customer information so that such third parties can promote their products and services. You may decline this opportunity in the Account Information section.

**Security Policy**

Customer information is protected by 128 bit SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption both at Warmoth.com and our credit card processor. We use this SSL technology to prevent your information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet and is the current standard for credit card security on the Internet today.

Further, you access your Warmoth account information through double verification of your email address and password. When a new Warmoth.com account is created, we require you to submit an e-mail address that is not associated with an existing Warmoth account. We do not allow any e-mail address to access more than one Warmoth.com account, and only you know your password. You can change this email address or password at anytime, once you are successfully logged in.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your email address, password and computer. To enhance security of your on-line purchasing we conduct daily security scans through a third party vendor. In addition, Warmoth Guitar Products, Inc. is fully compliant with the current security standards of the Payment Card Industry (PCI).

Please see the Conditions of Use for more information. By visiting Warmoth.com you are agreeing to the Conditions of Use and this Privacy and Security Policy.
